https://www.microflown.com/privacy

All Products
Wide range of sensors and systems for sound localization, sound power characterization, sound intensity, material testing, noise control, benchmarking and troubleshooting.
Sound Localization Systems
Sound Power & Source Ranking
Acoustic Material Testing
Portable Measuring Systems
Sensors & Probes
Software | Velo
Sound Sources | VVS
Sensor Arrays
Go back
Markets
All Markets
Microflown sensors and systems are used in many industrial sectors, from localizing sound sources with a high spatial resolution to quantifying acoustic emission via sound intensity and sound power even in non-anechoic conditions.
Automotive NVH & Ground Vehicles
Appliances & Electronics
Heavy Industry & Machinery
Aerospace & Aviation
End-Of-Line & Quality Control
Building acoustics
Education & Research
Go back
Support
All Support
A variety of support & service options are offered to ensure you will get what you need. Be it for maintenance of your equipment or support on a project you are doing, the Microfown team is ready to help you!
Software & Support Contracts
Calibration Service
Repair
Engineering Services
Go back
News
All News
Read more about our latest news
Firmware Voyager 2.0 is available!
Acoustic Webinars
Velo 5 is Launched!
Try your luck! Win Sony noise cancelling headphones
Testing Expo China 2019 Automotive
TRADE-IN & TRADE-UP | SCAN&PAINT 2D TO 3D
Microflown at NVH seminar of Multittech - Brazil
Product Catalog 2019 is now available
Go back
Case studies
All Case studies
All Careers
We are looking for talented and highly motivated people to join our team.
Embedded Software Engineer
Internship | Machine learning for acoustic quality control
Internship |
AI sound recognition and audio quality
Internship | Embedded Software Development
Internship | Active and Reactive intensity for NVH problems
Internship | Signal processing for acoustic vector sensors
Internship | Image processing for Sensor Tracking
Internship | In-situ Sound Transmission Loss
Go back
Resources
All Resources
A extensive range of information can be found in the Resources section. Diverse documents such as product documentation, application notes, scientific papers, e-books and more are freely accessible here.
Product Data
Product Leaflet
Full Product Catalog
Scientific Papers
Publication List
E-books
Open Acoustic Datasets
Videos
Go back
About us
Based upon its unique MEMS acoustic particle velocity sensor, Microflown Technologies develops and markets highly innovative products and testing services in the field of sound and vibration.
Read more
Go back
Contact us
Use the form to contact us at any time
Read more
Menu
ACOUSTIC SENSORS & MEASURING SOLUTIONS
Home
Privacy
Privacy
Welcome to our website. If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of us.The term 'Microflown Technologies' or 'us' or 'we' refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is Tivolilaan 205, 6834 BV Arnhem, The Netherlands. Our company registration number is 28077207 The term 'you' refers to the user or viewer of our website.Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how Microflown Technologies uses and protects any information that you give Microflown Technologies when you use this website.Microflown Technologies is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.Microflown Technologies may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.What we collectWe may collect the following information when you registrate for our newsletters, create a login profile or fill in the contact form:name and job titlecontact information including email addressdemographic information such as addressother information relevant to customer surveys and/or offersSecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.How we use cookiesThis website uses “cookies”.A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Controlling your personal informationWe will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties.If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write an email to info@microflown.com. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.CopyrightThis website, its webdesign and its content is a copyright of Microflown Technologies - © Microflown Technologies 2010-2018. All rights reserved.
ACOUSTIC SENSORS & MEASURING SOLUTIONS
